A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA386b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Central America, 1930-1947; 420; 2 Cubic Feet; 5 __Boxes __2 cubic feet
  - Central America - Public Health Demonstrations, 420.J
    - (Local Health Units), 1930-1940 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Central America - Health Services, 420.K
    - MAG-3 Magoon, Estus H. "Brief Outline of Operations During May 1930" (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - MOL-1 Molloy, D. M. and Magoon, E. H. "The Making of Pre-cast Concrete Inverts for Paving Drainage Ditches", 1936 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Public Health Laboratories, 1931-1941 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Sanitary Engineering, 1931-1937 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Central America - Public Health Education, 420.L
    - Public Health Education, 1931-1935 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Central America - Yellow Fever, 420.O
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1942 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- British Guiana (Guyana), 1937-1947; 423; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
  Rockefeller Foundation activity in Guyana was limited to malaria and yellow fever work in the years 1938-1947. This series also contains reports on sanitation (1941) and tuberculosis (1940) in this country.
  423 I Malaria
  423 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering)
  423 O Yellow fever
  423 T Tuberculosis
  - British Guiana (Guyana) - Malaria, 423.I
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - (Malaria), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - (Malaria) - Reports, 1937, 1946-1947; 3 items contained in folders 7-8. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - (Malaria) - Reports, 1937, 1946-1947; 3 items contained in folders 7-8. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - British Guiana (Guyana) - Health Services, 423.K
    - FOX Fox, Leon A. "Sanitary Survey of British Guiana", 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - British Guiana (Guyana) - Yellow Fever, 423.O
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - (Yellow Fever), 1938-1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - British Guiana (Guyana) - Tuberculosis, 01.0001/423.T
    - WE-1 Wells, Clifford W. "A Report on the Tuberculosis Problem in British Guiana", 1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Canada, 1914, 1917-1957; 427; 14 Cubic Feet; 35 __Boxes __14 cubic feet
  The first Foundation grant to Canada was as part of a relief effort in Newfoundland (1914). As part of regular program oriented support, the Foundation supported various medical and public health projects, especially between 1920 and 1950. Dalhousie and McGill University, the Universities of Manitoba and Montreal, and various Provincial governments were the main beneficiaries of the Foundation's interests in these areas.
  In the humanities, the Foundation gave grants for folklore studies, library surveys, and drama, mainly in the 1940's. Support for the social sciences came mainly through grants and fellowships administered by the Canadian social Science Research Council (1940-1957) and various universities.
  Ten subseries as follows:
  427 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  427 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  427 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing)
  427 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  427 J Public health demonstrations, local health units
  427 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering)
  427 L Public health education (schools of hygiene and public health)
  427 R Humanities and arts
  427 S Social sciences
  427 T Tuberculosis
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1920-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Reports, 1926-1938; 11 items (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Canadian National Research Council, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Canadian National Research Council, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Manitoba - Industrial Hygiene, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Manitoba - Industrial Hygiene, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Manitoba - Industrial Hygiene, 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Manitoba - Industrial Hygiene, 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission, 1917-1933 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts - Halifax Health Commission - Reports, 1918-1929; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New Brunswick - Health, 1937-1939, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New Brunswick - Health, 1937-1939, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - New Brunswick - Nutrition, 1943-1948 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Newfoundland Sealing Disaster, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Quebec - Industrial Hygiene and Nutrition, 1935-1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever, 1937-1944 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sylvatic Plague and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever - Report, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Canada - Medical Sciences, 427.A
    - Canada - Medical Education - Historical Record - CAN, 1919-1925 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Dalhousie University - Historical Record - DAL, 1919-1927, 1934, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Dalhousie University - Psychiatry, 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Dalhousie University - Psychiatry, 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Dalhousie University - Psychiatry, 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Dalhousie University - Psychiatry, 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Dalhousie University - Psychiatry, 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Dalhousie University - Public Health Teaching, 1926-1930, 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Dalhousie University - Public Health Teaching, 1926-1930, 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Dalhousie University - Public Health Teaching, 1926-1930, 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Dalhousie University - Public Health Teaching, 1926-1930, 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Dalhousie University - Public Health Teaching, 1926-1930, 1932-1944 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Dalhousie University - Victoria General Hospital Survey, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Dalhousie University - Victoria General Hospital Survey - Report, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Dalhousie University - Victoria Hospital, 1941-1954 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Dalhousie University - Victoria Hospital, 1941-1954 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - McGill University - Endocrinology, 1934-1951 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - McGill University - Endocrinology, 1934-1951 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - McGill University - Endocrinology, 1934-1951 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - McGill University - Endocrinology, 1934-1951 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - McGill University - Epilepsy, 1938-1952 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - McGill University - Epilepsy, 1938-1952 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - McGill University - Faculty of Medicine - Historical Record - McGU FM, 1919-1925, 1934, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - McGill University - Faculty of Medicine - Historical Record - McGU FM, 1919-1925, 1934, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 0055A)
    - McGill University - Faculty of Medicine - Historical Record - McGU FM, 1919-1925, 1934, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 0055B)
    - McGill University - Fleming, Grant - (Visits, Public Health), 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - McGill University - Neurology, 1931-1939 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - McGill University - Neurology, 1931-1939 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - McGill University - Neurology, 1931-1939 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - McGill University - Neurology, 1931-1939 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - McGill University - Neurology, 1931-1939 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - McGill University - Neurology - Reports and Pamphlets, 1935-1936; 3 items (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - McGill University - Surgical Research - Historical Record - McGU SR, 1928-1935 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - McGill University - Visit, McDonald, R. St. John - (Public Health) - McGU, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Royal Victoria Hospital - Lynch, Catherine - (Visits, Psychiatric Nursing), 1944 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - University of Alberta - Clinical Branches - Historical Record - UA CB, 1920-1925,1934,1937 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - University of Alberta - Rankin, Allen C. - (Visits, Public Health), 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - University of Alberta - Scott, John W. - (Visits, Public Health), 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - University of Manitoba - Bell, Lennox F. - (Visits, Public Health), 1949-1953 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - University of Manitoba - Jackson, F. W. - (Visits, Public Health), 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - University of Manitoba - Medical Faculty - Historical Record - Volume I - UMa MF, 1919-1937 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - University of Manitoba - Medical Faculty - Historical Record - Volume II - UMa MF, 1919-1934 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - University of Manitoba - Preventive Medicine, 1928-1940, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - University of Manitoba - Preventive Medicine, 1928-1940, 1942-1947 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - University of Montreal - Faculty of Medicine - Historical Record - UMo MF, 1920-1930 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - University of Montreal - Physiology - (Laugier, Henri; Refugee), 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - University of Montreal - Physiology - (Laugier, Henri; Refugee), 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - University of Montreal - Physiology - (Laugier, Henri; Refugee)- Refugee, 1941-1943; 6 items (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - University of Toronto - Medical Faculty - Historical Record - UT MF, 1919-1930 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - University of Toronto - Pediatrics, 1929-1935 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1943-1948 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry, 1943-1948 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry - Reports, 1939-1941; 13 items (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - University of Toronto - Psychiatry - Supplementary Material, 1932-1947 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Canada - Nursing, 427.C
    - University of British Columbia - Nursing and Health, 1936-1942 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - University of British Columbia - Nursing and Health, 1936-1942 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - University of British Columbia - Nursing and Health, 1936-1942 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - University of Toronto - School of Nursing - Reprints and Reports, 1928-1936; 6 items (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 427.D
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - McGill University - Genetics, 1936-1946 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - McGill University - Holtfreter, Johann - (Refugee, Embryology), 1941-1944 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - McGill University - Holtfreter, Johann - (Refugee, Embryology), 1941-1944 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - McGill University - Spectroscopic Biology, 1933-1940 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - McGill University - Spectroscopic Biology, 1933-1940 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - McGill University - Spectroscopic Biology, 1933-1940 (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - McGill University - Spectroscopic Biology - Report & Supplementary Material, 1934-1936; 4 items (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - McGill University - Stehle, Raymond L. - (Pharmacology), 1934-1938 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - University of Alberta - Organic Chemistry, 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - University of Alberta - Organic Chemistry, 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - University of Alberta - Zoology, 1940-1942 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - University of Alberta - Zoology, 1940-1942 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition, 1939-1953 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition - Report, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - University of Toronto - Nutrition - Reprints, 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - University of Toronto - Respiration, 1936-1937 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Canada - Public Health Demonstrations, 427.J
    - Alberta, 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Alberta, 1931-1941 (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - Alberta, 1931-1941 (Box 16, Folder 146)
    - Alberta, 1931-1941 (Box 16, Folder 147)
    - Alberta - Report, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 151)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - British Columbia, 1928-1935 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 158)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - British Columbia, 1936-1949 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    - British Columbia - Reports, 1933-1936; 8 items (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - British Columbia - Reports, 1937-1941; 4 items (Box 18, Folder 165)
    - Manitoba, 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 166)
    - Manitoba, 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 167)
    - Manitoba, 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - Manitoba, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Manitoba, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - Manitoba, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - Manitoba, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    - Manitoba, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - Manitoba - Local Health Services, 1941-1947 (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - Manitoba - Local Health Services, 1941-1947 (Box 19, Folder 175)
    - Nova Scotia, 1933-1940 (Box 19, Folder 176)
    - Nova Scotia, 1933-1940 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    - Nova Scotia, 1933-1940 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    - Nova Scotia, 1933-1940 (Box 19, Folder 179)
    - Nova Scotia, 1933-1940 (Box 19, Folder 180)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 181)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 185)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 186)
    - Nova Scotia, 1941-1947 (Box 20, Folder 187)
    - Nova Scotia - Reports, 1934-1936, 1944; 5 items (Box 20, Folder 188)
    - Nova Scotia - Reports, 1934-1936, 1944; 5 items (Box 20, Folder 189)
    - Nova Scotia - Reports, 1934-1936, 1944; 5 items (Box 20, Folder 190)
    - Ontario, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 191)
    - Ontario, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - Ontario, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 193)
    - Ontario, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 194)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 195)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 196)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 197)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 198)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 199)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 200)
    - Quebec, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 201)
    - Quebec, 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - Quebec, 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - Quebec, 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - Quebec - Reports, 1936, 1939; 2 items contained in folders 205-206. (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - Quebec - Reports, 1936, 1939; 2 items contained in folders 205-206. (Box 22, Folder 206)
    - Quebec - Health Education, 1942-1947 (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - Saskatchewan, 1928-1933 (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - Saskatchewan, 1928-1933 (Box 22, Folder 209)
  - Canada - Health Services, 427.K
    - British Columbia, 1929-1936 (Box 22, Folder 210)
    - British Columbia, 1929-1936 (Box 22, Folder 211)
    - Manitoba - Vital Statistics, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 212)
    - Manitoba - Vital Statistics, 1938-1949 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Manitoba - Vital Statistics, 1938-1949 (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - Manitoba - Vital Statistics, 1938-1949 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - Manitoba - Vital Statistics - Reprints, 1940-1941; 2 Items (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - New Brunswick, 1946-1953 (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Nova Scotia - Sanitary Engineering, 1934-1940 (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - Nova Scotia - Vital Statistics and Epidemiology, 1934-1942 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Nova Scotia - Vital Statistics and Epidemiology, 1934-1942 (Box 23, Folder 220)
    - Prince Edward Island - Public Health Laboratory, 1938-1939, 1942-1951 (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - Prince Edward Island - Public Health Laboratory, 1938-1939, 1942-1951 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - Prince Edward Island - Public Health Laboratory - Report, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - Quebec, 1931-1934 (Box 23, Folder 224)
  - Canada - Public Health Education, 427.L
    - Canadian Health Executives - (Travel), February - August 1941 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Canadian Health Executives - (Travel), February - August 1941 (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - New Brunswick, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 227)
    - Ontario - Training of Personnel, 1941-1944 (Box 24, Folder 228)
    - Ontario - Training of Personnel, 1941-1944 (Box 24, Folder 229)
    - Quebec - Beauce County Training Station, 1929-1932 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene, 1924-1939 (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene, 1924-1939 (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene, 1924-1939 (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene - Reports, 1922-1939; 5 items (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene - Faculty Salaries, 1939-1951 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene - Faculty Salaries, 1939-1951 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene - Faculty Salaries, 1939-1951 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - University of Toronto - School of Hygiene - Faculty Salaries, 1939-1951 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - University of Toronto - Training Area, 1937-1952 (Box 25, Folder 239)
    - University of Toronto - Training Area, 1937-1952 (Box 25, Folder 240)
    - University of Toronto - Training Area, 1937-1952 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - University of Toronto - Training Area, 1937-1952 (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 427.R
    - Bibliotheque Municipale - Microfilm Reader, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - Canadian Association for Adult Education - Radio Study, 1941-1946 (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - Canadian Association for Adult Education - Radio Study, 1941-1946 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Canadian Association for Adult Education - Radio Study - Pamphlets, 1941-1946; 32 items (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - Canadian Drama Survey, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 247)
    - Canadian Drama Survey, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 248)
    - Canadian Drama Survey - Reports, 1942; 2 items (Box 25, Folder 249)
    - Canadian Humanities Research Council - Visit, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 250)
    - Canadian Library Council, 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Canadian Library Council, 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Canadian Library Council, 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Canadian Library Council, 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - Canadian Library Council - Pamphlets, 1943-1948; 13 items (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Canadian Libraries Survey, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 256)
    - Canadian Libraries Survey, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 257)
    - Canadian Libraries Survey - Report, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 258)
    - Laval University - Hughes, Everett C. - (Visit, Sociology), 1942-1948 (Box 26, Folder 259)